--- original text ---
Draft a professional email addressed to Alex Rodriguez in regards to another employee, Sarah Collins. Inform him that Sarah is going to be MIA for a while, due to recent health complications, and that she will be staying at the Portland Clinic for at least a few months. Let Alex know that he needs to update her HR records (her employee ID is 0048812) to reflect she is taking medical leave. Also, tell him to ensure her recorded home address is up to date. It should be 77 River Road, Springfield, IL 62704. Finally, sign the email with my name, David Kim, and my cell, (212)555-7890.

--- presidio text ---
Draft a professional email addressed to <PERSON> in regards to another employee, <PERSON>. Inform him that <PERSON> is going to be MIA for a while, due to recent health complications, and that she will be staying at the Portland Clinic for <DATE_TIME>. Let <PERSON> know that he needs to update her HR records (her employee ID is <DATE_TIME>) to reflect she is taking medical leave. Also, tell him to ensure her recorded home address is up to date. It should be <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>, IL 62704. Finally, sign the email with my name, <PERSON>, and my cell, <PHONE_NUMBER>.

--- gemma4 text ---
Draft a professional email addressed to <PERSON_A> in regards to another employee, <PERSON_B>. Inform him that <PERSON_B> is going to be MIA for a while, due to recent health complications, and that she will be staying at the <LOCATION_A> for at least a few months. Let <PERSON_A> know that he needs to update her HR records (her employee ID is <ID_NUMBER_A>) to reflect she is taking medical leave. Also, tell him to ensure her recorded home address is up to date. It should be <ADDRESS_A>. Finally, sign the email with <PERSON_C>, and my cell, <PHONE_NUMBER_B>.